

# FRANCISCO **AGUIRRE**

JR FULL STACK DEVELOPER







#### **Email**

franmaguirre@gmail.com



#### Tel de contacto

+54 9 0351-156140453



#### C Link GitHub



#### Ubicación

Ingeniero López 275, Córdoba, Argentina

#### PERFIL

Desarrollador Full Stack Jr. bilingüe (Inglés-Castellano). Me apasiona la creación de diseños web escalables, responsivos y dinámicos que mejoren la experiencia del usuario y estimulen el crecimiento del negocio. Me encanta crear proyectos desafiantes utilizando programación funcional, orientados a facilitar el testing y la depuración en el proceso del ciclo de desarrollo. Soy de Córdoba, Argentina y nací el 8 de Julio de 1988 (34).

## **EDUCACIÓN**

2022 - Presente

Python | Javascript FreeCodeCamp | Scrimba

2022 - 2023

**Full Stack .NET Developer** 

ISPC - Cba - Arg

2007 - 2012

Traductorado de Inglés

UNC - Cba - Arg

## LENGUAJES DE PROGRAMACIÓN / **HERRAMIENTAS**

JavaScript

Typescript (Angular)

HTML | CSS | GIT

SQL (SQL Server | MySQL)

Bootstrap (UI)

Angular Material (UI)

C# (.NET)

### EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

# **Encode SA (Software Factory -**Firma Digital)

2022 - 2023

- Escribir código limpio y probable usando lenguaje C# para back end, typescript para Front y SQL para gestión de bases de datos.
- Probar y depurar diversas aplicaciones de .NET.
- Revisar y refactorizar el código.

#### **Proyectos Freelance**

2021 - 2023

- https://franciscoaguirrefrontendapp.netlify.app
- https://franciscoaguirreauthlogin.netlify.app
- https://franciscoaguirre-e-commercesite.netlify.app/products

# Soporte Técnico Nivel - Encode 2021 - 2023 SA

- Soporte Técnico remoto para usuarios de firma digital.
- Configuración de sistemas operativos e instalación
- de paquetes y controladores.



# FRANCISCO **AGUIRRE**

JR FULL STACK DEVELOPER



in Link LinkedIn



**Email** 

franmaguirre@gmail.com



Tel de contacto

+54 9 0351-156140453





**Ubicación** 

Ingeniero López 275, Córdoba, Argentina

#### **PROFILE**

As a Jr Full Stack Software Developer with advanced english-spanish skills, I am passionate about developing innovative solutions that enhance user experiences and drive business growth. With a solid foundation in front-end and back-end development, I have experience building dynamic web applications and responsive mobile interfaces.

#### **EDUCATION**

2022- Present

**Python for Data Science Cognitive Class** 

2022 - 2023

**Full Stack .NET Developer** Polytechnic Institute (Cba)

2007 - 2012

**ENG-SP Translation -**

National University at Córdoba

# **PROGRAMMING** LANGUAGES AND TOOLS

JavaScript

Typescript (Angular)

HTML | CSS | GIT

SQL (SQL Server | MySQL)

Bootstrap (UI)

Angular Material (UI)

C# (.NET)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Encode (Software Factory - Digital** Signature)

2022 - 2023

- C# / SQL / Angular
- Full stack Projects using C# for backend, SQL Server and Angular (Typescript) for frontend
- · Web API calls and microservices use

#### **Freelance Projects**

2021 - 2023

- https://franciscoaguirrefrontendapp.netlify.app
- · https://franciscoaguirreauthlogin.netlify.app
- · https://franciscoaguirre-e-commercesite.netlify.app/products

# Technical Support - Encode 2021 - 2023 (Software Factory)

- Remote assistance for digital signature software clients
- Operative systems setup and browser security configuration
- Packages installation procedures to ensure correct setup environment for our products